Rieko Radomski

Cell: 862-213-9676 | Email: rieko.radomski@gmail.com

Portfolio: hibacostudio.com

Profile

Innovative Freelance Graphic Designer, Web Designer, Illustrator, and Editor with 10 years and over working experience in digital and print industries. Expert in the management of the complete design process from conceptualization to delivery. Multi-task taker with passion for design, excellent communication and keen proofreading skills.

Professional Experience

Freelance Designer | International Academy of Arts and Sciences, Closter, NJ | 2012 - Present

- Delivered and running NJ based preschool website <u>www.asunarokokusai.org</u> using HTML and CSS.
- Created successful promotional products, including brochures, postcard and newspaper advertisements, and school logo, written in English and Japanese.
- Took photos and edited images for print and online promotional use.

Senior Book Editor/Illustrator | Peoples Publishing Group, Saddle Brook, NJ | 2002 – 2005

- Set layouts and supervised all the design aspects of the Measuring Up textbooks and test materials.
- Created a wide variety of hand-drawn and digitally enhanced illustrations for textbooks and tests.

Designer/Editor/Writer | Miyanjoe International Ltd., New York, NY | 1998 – 2001

- Set layouts for the entertainment monthly magazines and guidebooks for Broadway shows; delivered print-ready materials for magazine covers in four-color and wrote articles for contents.
- Coordinated multiple tours and interviews for Japanese TV programs and occasional clients.

Education

BFA Graphic Design-Letterform | University of Massachusetts Dartmouth, Dartmouth, MA

Skills

- Proficiency in Adobe Creative Suite (InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop)
- Basic knowledge of Web Design/Coding (HTML and CSS)
- Skilled Hand Drawing techniques
- Fluent in English and Japanese